<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FarmGame</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">MainMenuActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_farm">FarmActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">HelpActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_high_score">HighScoreActivity</string>

    <string name="silo_shop_button_text">Silo/Shop</string>
    <string name="item_detail_title">Item Details:</string>
    <string name="button_buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="button_sell">Sell</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="array_crops">
        <item name="wheat">wheat</item>
        <item name="corn">corn</item>
        <item name="potato">potato</item>
        <item name="strawberry">strawberry</item>
        <item name="not_now">not now</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="plant_a_seed">Plant a seed</string>
    <string name="close_list">Close</string>
    <integer name="cornMutureTime">6001</integer>
    <integer name="wheatMutureTime">4001</integer>
    <integer name="strawberryMutureTime">20001</integer>
    <integer name="potatoMutureTime">10001</integer>

    <string name="LOGIN_PREFS">farmgame.PREFS</string>
    <string name="LOGGEDIN">login</string>
    <string name="SharedPreference_currentUser">SharedPreference_currentUser</string>
    <string name="LOGIN_FILE">farmgame.LOGIN_FILE</string>
    <string name="action_logout">log out</string>
    <string name="action_load">load</string>
    <string name="action_save">save</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1605744539743264</string>
    <string name="send_email">email friends</string>
    <string name="pleaseEnterAnEmail">Please enter your friend\'s email to share your high score:</string>
    <string name="emailExample">example@uw.edu</string>
    <string name="help_button">Help</string>
    <string name="parts_of_main_screen">Main Screen:\n
1:  Level-this is your current level. You level-up automatically when you gain experience.\n
2:  Money-this is how much money you currently have. You can sell crops and use money to buy crops in the Silo/Shop.\n
3:  Experience-this is how much experience you currently have. You gain experience by harvesting crops.\n
4:  Fields-these are the fields you can plant crops in.  You gain more by leveling up.</string>
    <string name="getting_started">Getting Started:\n
If this is your first time playing you will only have 3 fields.  You also have 0 money but don\'t despair,
        you have enough wheat to plant one of your fields.  You click on one of the fields and the seed
        selector will appear.  The seed selector will show the seeds you have in your inventory and how many
        of each you have.  When you click on the seed you would like to have planted, it begins to grow in the
        field that you had selected.  Once the crop is done growing, it will say \"Ready!\" and all you have to
        do to harvest it is click on it.  When you harvest, several things are happening, first, you get at
        least 1 and at most 3 seeds back.  Second, your experience goes up.  Your experience increases based
        on the type of crop you harvested.  When your experience points get beyond 10 points, you level up and
        your experience points are docked 10 points.  When you level up you gain 1 extra farm field for each
        level.  After you have grown enough wheat you can click on the Silo/Shop button where you can see a
        full list of all crops and how many you have of each.  Since you don\'t have any money yet, you need
        to click on the wheat crop which you should now have several of.  Sell some of your wheat (best to
        keep some just in case) and now you have some money to buy a different type of crop.  Now you know
        the basics.  Good Luck!</string>

</resources>
